Taiowa Waner

Senior Integration Consultant at DayNine Consulting, Inc.

t.waner@gmail.com

Summary

I am a consultant who has found a true passion working with the latest technologies. In my work as a consultant I've worked with vendors and clients to deliver creative solutions to their specific problems. I use logic and problem solving to create solutions that allow internal and external enterprise size systems to communicate with each other. In addition, I am taking the first offering of Udacity's iOS Nano degree. I am learning best practices, how to craft high quality code and create apps to list on the App Store.

Experience

Integration Consultant at DayNine Consulting, Inc.

April 2014 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Interfacing with clients and vendors to access their needs and deliver a solution that will meet them. Designing and creating Workday integrations that interface with internal and external systems.

Software Engineer at Liberty Security Services

June 2013 - Present (2 years)

Design and implement CMS application using Django and Python. Integrate web based applications with SQL backend.

Software Quality Assurance at Symbotic

July 2012 - April 2014 (1 year 10 months)

Integrate automation software within a supply chain environment. Create, execute, and maintain automated and manual test cases on individual and interconnected software components. Participate in software design process. Work with contractors on software design and testing. Create manuals for integrating software components.

Automated System Operator at C&S Wholesale Grocers

June 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 2 months)

Managed automated warehouse system using Linux and Windows based proprietary software. Used SQL to create reports and respond to real time issues. Used Bash and Perl scripts to create system summary outputs that could be run by warehouse personnel for reporting and trouble shooting. Managed integration of supply chain software and hardware. Managed 6 warehouse staffers.

Business Manager at B and T Landscaping of Ulster County

September 2007 - May 2011 (3 years 9 months)

Created database to track customer information, account activity, and expenses. Used ETFs to hedge fuel costs. Created billing forms using Excel. Created algorithms for creating estimates for jobs.

Certifications

Workday Studio Certification

Workday June 2014

Workday Integration

Workday April 2014

Learn to Program: The Fundamentals

Coursera

Startup Engineering

Coursera September 2013

Beginning Game Programming with C#

Coursera November 2013

An Introduction to Interactive Programming in Python

Coursera Verified Certificates License VC79CF9D94 December 2013

Web Application Architectures

Coursera Verified Certificates License KF5W6LHCBY September 2014

Workday CCB Certification

Workday March 2015

Skills & Expertise

Swift

SQL

Linux

Troubleshooting

Software Design

Visual Studio

Visual C#

Databases

Workday Studio

Ubuntu

Bash

OS X

Visio

Oracle Applications

NetBeans

Xcode

Objective-C

Microsoft Excel

asana

JIRA

PHP

Python

Django

PyCharm

Version One

MySQL

SQLite

PostgreSQL

JavaScript

jQuery

SOAP

Parse

Workday Report Designer

BIRT

Education

Udacity

iOS Developer Nanodegree, Computer Software Engineering, 2015 - 2015

SUNY Empire State College

Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer Science, 2011 - 2013

SUNY New Paltz

Bachelor of Science (BS), Finance, General, 2002 - 2006

Activities and Societies: New Paltz Oracle

Projects

On The Map

April 2015 to May 2015

Members:Taiowa Waner

An app that allows the user to log into Udacity with their credentials. The user can view the locations of other students on a map; update their location and post a link of their choice; and view a list of students on a table view.

Languages

English

Taiowa Waner

Senior Integration Consultant at DayNine Consulting, Inc.

t.waner@gmail.com



Contact Taiowa on LinkedIn